<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>nursing &#8211; Home</title>
	<atom:link href="https://igernahan.netlify.app/index.php/tag/nursing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://igernahan.netlify.app</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 04:30:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Women&#8217;s Tuck-in Top/Jogger Scrub Set Medical Nursing GT 4FLEX Top and Pant</title>
		<link>https://igernahan.netlify.app/index.php/2022/11/30/womens-tuck-in-top-jogger-scrub-set-medical-nursing-gt-4flex-top-and-pant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 04:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Products]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4flex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apparel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nursing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[products]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scrub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[set]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top/jogger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tuck-in]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[womens]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://igernahan.netlify.app/index.php/2022/11/30/womens-tuck-in-top-jogger-scrub-set-medical-nursing-gt-4flex-top-and-pant/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Price: (as of &#8211; Details) Be prepared for whatever your workday has to offer in this sporty, yet professional womens scrub set. Stay on-trend in this modern uniform that includes a tuck-in scrub top and slim-fit jogger scrub pant. Built to last, this wrinkle resistant, non-see-through fabric is machine washable and will hold up after ... <a title="Women&#8217;s Tuck-in Top/Jogger Scrub Set Medical Nursing GT 4FLEX Top and Pant" class="read-more" href="https://igernahan.netlify.app/index.php/2022/11/30/womens-tuck-in-top-jogger-scrub-set-medical-nursing-gt-4flex-top-and-pant/" aria-label="More on Women&#8217;s Tuck-in Top/Jogger Scrub Set Medical Nursing GT 4FLEX Top and Pant">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p>
<p>Price: <span style="color:#b12704">$32.99</span><br /><i><small>(as of Nov 30,2022 04:30:31 UTC &#8211; <span class="wp_automatic_amazon_disclaimer" title="Product prices and availability are accurate as of the date/time indicated and are subject to change. Any price and availability information displayed on [relevant Amazon Site(s), as applicable] at the time of purchase will apply to the purchase of this product.">Details</span>)</small></i></p>
<p><a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0BL3YLYBV?tag=arestepz-20"><img decoding="async" src="https://i.imgur.com/ISRHEWs.png"></a><br />
  <span>Be prepared for whatever your workday has to offer in this sporty, yet professional womens scrub set. Stay on-trend in this modern uniform that includes a tuck-in scrub top and slim-fit jogger scrub pant. Built to last, this wrinkle resistant, non-see-through fabric is machine washable and will hold up after multiple washings. This versatile womens scrub top can be worn tucked in or out for a variety of trendy looks. The slim-fit jogger scrub pant features an elastic jogger hem and a full elastic and full drawstring closure waistband that stays secure on the waist. Offering a 93% Polyester and 7% Spandex blend with reinforced seams and stitching, designed to make you feel comfortable with four way stretch material. The perfect blend of style, comfort, and fit.</span>  <br /> Package Dimensions                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 13.5 x 10.28 x 1.5 inches; 11.78 Ounces <br /> Item model number                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 817 <br /> Date First Available                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 November 1, 2022 <br /> Manufacturer                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 Green Town <br /> ASIN                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 B0BL418C7Q </p>
<p>Drawstring closure<br />2-PIECE SET: Be work-ready in the affordably priced GT 4FLEX scrub set. The tuckable V-Neck uniform top offers one chest pocket and one utility pocket to help hold your gear. The jogger scrub pant features two slash hip pockets and two cargo pockets, a drawstring, and an elastic waist band that adjusts to your fit. Experience maximum comfort in this lightweight, extremely soft material. Perfect for any nurse, doctor, physician assistant, dentist, med student, and more!<br />FUNCTIONAL YET FASHIONABLE: If you are looking to add fashion and functionality to your uniform collection, this scrub set is just for you! Pairs perfectly with joggers, the cute &#038; trendy scrub top can be worn both tucked and untucked to add versatility to your look. Dress this jogger pant up or down, perfect for working out or lounging around on your days off. The ultimate uniform for all women healthcare professionals, the super-soft construction of this scrub set will make it your new go-to!<br />USEFUL FEATURES: This scrub set is a must-have essential! This womens uniform set comes equipped with 6 functional pockets overall. Ideal for the medical field, the scrub top features a spacious chest pocket and a convenient utility pocket for your instruments. Also offering side vents created for increased mobility and ease of movement. Pockets for the pants are 2 functional slash hip pockets and 2 convenient utility cargo pockets. Meet all your storage needs with maximized pocket space.<br />WASH AND WEAR: Machine Wash Safe, Easy To Clean, Dries Fast, and Shrink Resistant! Built to last, this high-quality fabric is machine washable and will hold up after multiple washings. Maintain a clean and professional look in this wrinkle resistant, non-see-through fabric. Be crease and crinkle free with little to no ironing needed!<br />STRETCH FABRICATION: A high-quality, soft, and breathable fabric made to move when you move. Offering a 93% Polyester and 7% Spandex blend constructed with reinforced seams and stitching. Designed to make you feel comfortable, this top provides extra-durable, four way stretch material. Ensure lasting comfort and wider range of motion throughout your entire workday. </p>
<p>Price: <span style="color:#b12704">$32.99</span><br /><i><small>(as of Nov 30,2022 04:30:31 UTC &#8211; <span class="wp_automatic_amazon_disclaimer" title="Product prices and availability are accurate as of the date/time indicated and are subject to change. Any price and availability information displayed on [relevant Amazon Site(s), as applicable] at the time of purchase will apply to the purchase of this product.">Details</span>)</small></i></p>
<p><a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0BL3YLYBV?tag=arestepz-20"><img decoding="async" src="https://i.imgur.com/ISRHEWs.png"></a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
