<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>tackle &#8211; Home</title>
	<atom:link href="https://igernahan.netlify.app/index.php/tag/tackle/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://igernahan.netlify.app</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 03:49:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Columbia Men&#8217;s Terminal Tackle Long Sleeve Shirt</title>
		<link>https://igernahan.netlify.app/index.php/2022/11/30/columbia-mens-terminal-tackle-long-sleeve-shirt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 03:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Products]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apparel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[columbia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[long]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[products]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shirt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sleeve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tackle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terminal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://igernahan.netlify.app/index.php/2022/11/30/columbia-mens-terminal-tackle-long-sleeve-shirt/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Price: (as of &#8211; Details) WIth Collegiate flair, the polyester interlock construction of our PFG Terminal Tackle Long Sleeve Shirt offers full coverage against harmful midday sun with UPF 50 protection. It showcases your college spirit. It’s lightweight and quick drying, making it the perfect solution for staying cool while protecting your skin out over ... <a title="Columbia Men&#8217;s Terminal Tackle Long Sleeve Shirt" class="read-more" href="https://igernahan.netlify.app/index.php/2022/11/30/columbia-mens-terminal-tackle-long-sleeve-shirt/" aria-label="More on Columbia Men&#8217;s Terminal Tackle Long Sleeve Shirt">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p>
<p>Price: <span style="color:#b12704">$8.25</span><br /><i><small>(as of Nov 30,2022 03:49:52 UTC &#8211; <span class="wp_automatic_amazon_disclaimer" title="Product prices and availability are accurate as of the date/time indicated and are subject to change. Any price and availability information displayed on [relevant Amazon Site(s), as applicable] at the time of purchase will apply to the purchase of this product.">Details</span>)</small></i></p>
<p><a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07ZZSH178?tag=arestepz-20"><img decoding="async" src="https://i.imgur.com/ISRHEWs.png"></a><br />
  <span>WIth Collegiate flair, the polyester interlock construction of our PFG Terminal Tackle Long Sleeve Shirt offers full coverage against harmful midday sun with UPF 50 protection. It showcases your college spirit. It’s lightweight and quick drying, making it the perfect solution for staying cool while protecting your skin out over any highly reflective water. The ultimate day-out-in-the-sun staple. This technology featured long sleeve is necessity for events on the ocean, lake, river, or campus side. Made up of a combination of Columbia’s signature protection fabrics: UPF 50 works to block and shield you from harmful UVA and UVB sun rays known to cause skin damage, while the advanced wicking fabric works to pull moisture and water away from the skin. You remain cool while our signature PFG logo runs along the sleeve. Columbia offers this fishing shirt with a range of college logos and in a variety of sizes. Regular Fit. To ensure the size you choose is right, utilize our sizing chart and the following measurement instructions: For the sleeves, start at the center back of your neck and measure across the shoulder and down to the sleeve. If you come up with a partial number, round up to the next even number. For the chest, measure at the fullest part of the chest, under the armpits and over the shoulder blades, keeping the tape measure firm and level.</span>  <br /> Package Dimensions                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 14.29 x 10.94 x 1.46 inches; 7.05 Ounces <br /> Item model number                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 1892211 <br /> Date First Available                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 January 4, 2020 <br /> Manufacturer                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 Columbia <br /> ASIN                                    ‏                                        :                                    ‎                                 B07ZZSH5YC </p>
<p>Imported<br />Pull On closure<br />OMNI-SHADE: Be safe and protected. Omni-Shade blocks UVA and UVB rays to help prevent sunburns and long-term skin damage. The tight weave construction with UV absorbent yarns block the full spectrum of harmful UV rays<br />OMNI-WICK: The ultimate moisture management technology for the outdoors. Omni-Wick quickly moves moisture from the skin into the fabric where it spreads across the surface to quickly evaporate—keeping you cool and your clothing dry<br />ADVANCED PROTECTION: The Columbia Men’s PFG Terminal Tackle Long Sleeve Shirt guards against sun damage thanks to the built-in UPF 50 material. It’s a breathable, quick wicking fabric that pulls moisture away to keep you cool and dry<br />PFG COMFORT &#038; BREATHABILITY: Made from a polyester interlock quick-dry material, this fishing shirt is right at home on the water<br />CLASSIC FIT: This long sleeve Tee Shirt is designed for classic fit, built for ultimate comfortability in any adventure </p>
<p>4.5<br />
Price: <span style="color:#b12704">$8.25</span><br /><i><small>(as of Nov 30,2022 03:49:52 UTC &#8211; <span class="wp_automatic_amazon_disclaimer" title="Product prices and availability are accurate as of the date/time indicated and are subject to change. Any price and availability information displayed on [relevant Amazon Site(s), as applicable] at the time of purchase will apply to the purchase of this product.">Details</span>)</small></i></p>
<p><a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07ZZSH178?tag=arestepz-20"><img decoding="async" src="https://i.imgur.com/ISRHEWs.png"></a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
